<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>TwinDS</title>
    <link>https://twin-data-science.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on TwinDS</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>© TwinDS</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://twin-data-science.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Ferramentas importantes para começar</title>
      <link>https://twin-data-science.github.io/post/prerequisites/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twin-data-science.github.io/post/prerequisites/</guid>
      <description>Precisamos de algumas ferramentas instaladas e funcionando na sua máquina:
Utilize uma interface para Linha de Comando (Command Line Interface) Para desenvolver na sua máquina, você vai precisar acessar sua interface com a linha comando da sua máquina. Caso utilize macOS / linux, abra a aplicação Terminal. Se você é usuário de windows, abra o prompt de comando (&amp;lsquo;Command Prompt&amp;rsquo;).
Escolha um bom Editor de Texto Gosto de usar VSCodium, a versáo Free/Libre Open Source Software dos binários do editor de texto da Microsoft, VSCode (o código fonte do vscode contém telemetria/rastreamento).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Build your first Web App for Data Visualization</title>
      <link>https://twin-data-science.github.io/post/build-webapp/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twin-data-science.github.io/post/build-webapp/</guid>
      <description>Build your first Web App for Data Visualization using Vue.js!
In this article we&amp;rsquo;re using two modern tools for Data Visualization using Javascript:
 Vue.js - about vuejs eCharts - about echarts  Assumptions:  Minimal knowledge of Javascript; We are using free and open-source software package manager to simplify the installation of software. Here we&amp;rsquo;ll use Homebrew (macOS &amp;gt;= 10.14 or Linux). You can use other package manager for your OS or install Node and Yarn following their instructions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://twin-data-science.github.io/page/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twin-data-science.github.io/page/about/</guid>
      <description>This blog intends to share informative articles about our Data Science work, exploring interactions with different study fields and its impacts on economy, government and policy. Visit our Github!
About the team Hugo Honda I am a mission-driven Data Scientist and Full Stack developer focused on Python and Javascript. Currently Technology Coordinator at Neoway Business Solutions.
 More About Me  Iúri Honda  PhD Economics - PUC Rio / Columbia University More  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>